{
    "subject": "resource/Urapopstar",
    "predicate": "ontology/computingPlatform",
    "object": "resource/Web_browser",
    "human_readable": "Urapopstar uses a Web browser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9576823711395264,
            "question": "What activities might Urapopstar perform using a Web browser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219951629638672,
            "question": "How does Urapopstar's use of a Web browser impact their access to information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8995630741119385,
            "question": "What does Urapopstar use to access the internet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.821895956993103,
            "question": "What tool allows Urapopstar to explore online information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7798948287963867,
            "question": "How does Urapopstar likely view websites?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.679561972618103,
            "question": "What are some examples of websites that Urapopstar could visit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5398702621459961,
            "question": "Is Urapopstar likely using a mobile device or a computer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3368918299674988,
            "question": "What features are commonly found in Web browsers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2986566722393036,
            "question": "Can you name some popular Web browsers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20328694581985474,
            "question": "Why are Web browsers important for online communication and interaction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Urapopstar uses a Web browser.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9069_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some popular Web browsers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9069_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What features are commonly found in Web browsers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9069_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Urapopstar likely using a mobile device or a computer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9069_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9069_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Urapopstar as a \"multiplayer browser-based role-playing game,\" which confirms that it indeed uses a web browser."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Urapopstar is a browser-based game, not a web browser.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}